(Arthur:)If someone had told me that people
would still call me Professor Proton
(Arthur:)when I was 83 years old,
(Arthur:)I never would have quit smoking.
(Leonard:)I'm sorry, Dr. Jeffries,
I'm just excited.
(Leonard:)This nano vacuum tube idea
of yours, it's really interesting.
(Sheldon:)Hello, Leonard. Oh, hello, Arthur.
(Sheldon:)What an odd coincidence
that you're both here.
(Leonard:)Why is it odd?
(Sheldon:)Because as it just so happens,
I'm also spending the day
(Sheldon:)with a beloved children's
television science personality.
(Sheldon:)Isn't that right,
new friend and colleague,
(Sheldon:)Bill Nye the Science Guy.
(Sheldon:)Sorry, I replaced you
with a newer model.
(Bill Nye:)Wow, Arthur Jeffries.
(Bill Nye:)It's an honour to meet you.
(Bill Nye:)My show never would
have happened without yours.
(Arthur:)That's what I told my lawyers.
(Leonard:)Mr. Nye, hello. I'm sorry he got
you involved in this nonsense.
(Bill:)He said I'd be speaking to a class.